In the garden?
在花园？
Why drink alone?
为什么要一个人喝酒？
Let's drink together.
我们一起喝吧。
Dad, look at you.
爸爸，看看你。
I always talk about my childhood when I meet anyone.
当我见到任何人时，我总是谈论我的童年。
You are an adult.
你是一个成年人了。
I will never see you again either.
我也再也见不到你了。
Look at you now.
看看你现在。
Yaoyao knows better than me.
瑶瑶比我懂得多。
I want to go to the toilet.
我想去厕所。
I will go with you.
我跟你一起去。
Oh, by the way, I forgot to ask you.
哦对了，忘了问你了。
I...
我...
There are many in your phone
你的手机里有很多
Pictures of me as a child, right?
我小时候的照片吧？
Ada.
艾达.
Can you copy me?
你能复制我吗？
What?
什么？
My computer is infected
我电脑中毒了
The photo is gone.
照片不见了。
Incidentally,
顺便一提，
You must remember to protect
你一定要记得保护
Important data on your computer.
您计算机上的重要数据。
I have a firewall on my computer.
我的电脑上有防火墙。
The target is Huang Jiaming.
目标是黄家明。
All documents on your computer
电脑上的所有文档
Do you like to have a look?
你想看看吗？
School photos?
学校的照片？
Okay, uncle.
好的，叔叔。
Dad, here we go again.
爸爸，又来了。
what is it?
它是什么？
let's start.
开始吧。
OK
好的。
since then,
自那以后，
I became a Russian woman.
我变成了俄罗斯女人。
Who is this guy?
这个人是谁？
The one next to Zi Sheng.
子胜旁边的那个。
so?
所以？
Yeah.
呀呀。
stop. Let's drink.
停下来。我们喝吧。
No more drinking, no more drinking.
不能再喝酒了，不能再喝酒了。
My head feels a little dizzy today.
今天我的头有点晕。
no.
不是。
I didn't drink much, but I felt dizzy.
我没喝多少，但头很晕。
who knows.
谁知道。
group.
团。
I added more water.
我加了更多的水。
unnecessary.
不需要。
We've run out of water. Add more.
水用完了。添加更多。
group.
团。
What else do you need?
你还需要什么？
No.
不。
Pay.
支付。
OK
好的。
Pay. hurry up.
支付。快点。
Aren't you dizzy?
你不晕吗？
Take you home to rest.
带你回家休息。
We go home.
我们回家吧。
My head is a little dizzy.
我的头有点晕。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Sit where you are.
坐在你所在的地方。
Slow down, uncle.
慢点，叔叔。
Why is my head so dizzy?
为什么我的头这么晕？
16th floor.
16楼。
ten.
十。
16.
16.
1615.
1615.
achieved.
已达到。
slowly.
慢慢地。
Slow down, come on.
慢点，来吧。
Dad, you rest first, rest first.
爸爸，您先休息，先休息。
Take a short break.
短暂休息。
OK
好的。
I hit him, I hit him.
我打他，我打他。
Take off your shoes.
脱下鞋子。
take it easy.
别紧张。
Why are you getting worse at drinking?
为什么你喝酒的能力越来越差？
This is the task they gave me.
这是他们给我的任务。
No more medicine is needed now.
现在不需要再吃药了。
You will spend it.
你会花掉它。
not me.
不是我。
didn't you come
你没来吗
To spy on me?
来监视我？
Do you want me to do this?
你要我这么做吗？
Where are the seasons?
季节在哪里？
Copy all documents on your computer.
复制计算机上的所有文档。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
let me.
让我。
unnecessary.
不需要。
They want me.
他们想要我。
but...
但...
It's always this password.
始终是这个密码。
i don't expect
我不期望
We are still progressing to this stage.
我们仍在进展到这个阶段。
Are you two still there?
你们两个还在吗？
uncle.
叔叔。
We were discussing where to go.
我们正在讨论去哪里玩。
Don't play it too late.
别玩太晚了。
Yeah.
呀呀。
Dad, why are you awake?
爸爸你怎么醒了？
We will leave soon.
我们很快就会离开。
Go play.
去玩。
Be careful.
当心。
Okay, calm down.
好吧，冷静一下。
Don't be too late.
别太晚了。
go to sleep.
去睡觉。
hurry up.
赶快。
Yeah.
呀呀。
sorry.
对不起。
today's task
今天的任务
It is documented here.
它被记录在这里。
Can I go?
我可以去吗？
certainly.
当然。
Are you hungry?
你们饿了吗？
Let's have some evening snacks. hurry up.
我们吃点晚间小吃吧。快点。
is this real?
这是真的吗？
I'm a therapist. hurry up.
我是治疗师。快点。
The action team is really fast.
行动组的速度确实很快。
Hurry up and follow.
赶紧跟上。
Huang Zisheng menyelesaikan
Huang Zisheng menyelesaikan
This espionage operation.
这次的间谍行动。
OK
好的。
we must catch
我们必须抓住
The best way to approach Huang Jiaming.
接近黄家明的最好方式。
Huang Zisheng,
Huang Zisheng,
Become another special forces ace.
成为另一位特种部队王牌。
But I feel like this chess piece
但我感觉这颗棋子
Still unstable.
仍然不稳定。
Let him get used to it.
让他习惯吧。
I will tell Mr. Zhang.
我会告诉张先生。
Before reaching the next destination,
在到达下一个目的地之前，
We must control it.
我们必须控制它。
And one more thing.
还有一件事。
Yaoyao is back.
瑶瑶回来了。
very good.
非常好。
He will pay close attention to Huang Zicheng.
他会密切关注黄子成。
Yao Yao.
Yao Yao.
I think I really enjoyed it.
我想我真的很喜欢它。
The more you like it, the stronger your connection will be.
你越喜欢，你们的联系就越紧密。
Yaoyao will protect him.
瑶瑶会守护他的。
I won't let him do anything stupid.
不会让他做傻事。
sorry Sorry sorry.
对不起，对不起，对不起。
There is too much business in the hotel.
酒店里生意太多了。
Is there anything necessary?
有什么必要的吗
Do we work together?
我们一起工作？
Sit down, sit down, don't hesitate.
坐吧，坐吧，别犹豫。
Leader, leader.
领导者，领导者。
We have understood the situation.
我们已经了解了情况。
what do you two want to know
你们两个想知道什么
I will definitely tell everything.
我一定会说出一切。
Signal tower above the resort.
度假村上方的信号塔。
When was it built?
它什么时候建成的？
signal tower.
信号塔。
should
应该
Approved last year.
去年批准的。
Completed early this year.
今年年初完成。
What do you recommend installing?
您建议安装什么？
Yes, the customer reaction.
没错，客户的反应。
The signal is not good here.
这里信号不好。
we just want to improve
我们只是想改进
Hotel service quality.
酒店服务质量。
Who is responsible?
谁是负责的人？
It must be a telecommunications company.
一定是电信公司。
We can't do this.
我们不能这样做。
Who would normally protect him?
一般情况下谁会保护他呢？
And of course there are telecommunications companies.
当然还有电信公司。
When was the last maintenance?
上次维护是什么时候？
The specific time.
具体时间。
I'll have to look into it.
我必须调查一下。
but i don't remember
但我不记得了
somebody is coming
有人来了
leader
领导人
Excuse me
请问
what happened?
发生了什么？
At the signal tower.
在信号塔处。
someone is involved
有人参与其中
thereby endangering national security.
从而危害国家安全。
We're going to tear it down.
我们要把它拆掉。
how come?
怎么会？
leader
领导人
I really do not know.
我真的不知道。
Let's make it like this.
让我们把它变成这样。
you totally agree
你完全同意
All procedures and records
所有程序和记录
and all notes.
和所有的笔记。
I immediately ordered people to get ready.
我立即吩咐人做好准备。
Not in a hurry.
不着急。
Why run?
为什么要跑？
Sit there first.
先坐那儿吧。
Do you know this person?
你认识这个人吗？
Boss Han.
韩老板。
familiar.
熟悉的。
Indeed, he is
确实，他是
This is a seafood supplier
这是一家海鲜供应商
at our hotel.
在我们的酒店。
Always come to our hotel
总是来我们酒店
Vacation.
度假。
He came alone.
他一个人来的。
what i saw
我看到了什么
He was alone.
只有他一个人。
I've never met anyone else.
我从未见过其他人。
Are you familiar with it?
你熟悉吗？
Customer relations, customer relations.
客户关系，客户关系。
Can he get on the roof?
他能爬上屋顶吗？
so...
所以...
impossible.
不可能的。
Why did he climb on the roof?
他为什么爬上屋顶？
I found that he had climbed onto the roof.
我发现他已经爬上屋顶了。
So, that's it
那么，就是这样了
Negligence in my work.
我工作中的疏忽。
I have to take this seriously.
我必须认真对待这件事。
Leader, I promise
领导，我保证
The hotel we stayed in later
后来我们住的酒店
won't appear
不会出现
Same error.
同样的错误。
OK
好的。
Thank you for your cooperation.
谢谢您的合作。
That's how it should be, that's how it should be.
就该如此，就该如此。
Be careful on the road.
路上要小心。
Aura.
光环。
People from the National Security Bureau are here.
国安局的人来了。
They were checking the hotel's cell tower.
他们正在检查酒店的信号塔。
what happened?
发生了什么？
What did you say?
你说什么？
I'm definitely not talking about you.
我绝对不是在说你。
I told you the hotel needed it.
我告诉过你酒店需要它。
That's very good.
那挺好的。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
They won't find anything.
他们不会找到任何东西。
We have to find out.
我们必须找出答案。
What if it’s a building?
如果是建筑呢？
Nothing to do with the NSA.
与国安局无关。
This is the National Security Agency.
这是国家安全局。
This is no small matter.
这可不是小事。
By the way, Mr. Han.
顺便说一句，韩先生。
Does it have anything to do with you?
跟你有什么关系吗？
How can I hurt you?
我怎么能伤害你呢？
listen.
听。
I can't stand this problem.
我无法忍受这个问题。
Don't worry, you don't have to bear it.
别担心，你不必承受。
I'll take care of it.
我会处理的。
shut up.
住口。
this.
这。
From inside the signal tower,
从信号塔内部，
from the signal tower.
从信号塔。
For the military.
对于军队来说。
I have also reviewed this camera.
我也检查过这款相机。
It is nothing special.
没什么特别的。
I also checked the hard drive.
我也检查过硬盘。
Nothing
什么都没有啊
Maybe it's just been replaced.
也许它刚刚被更换。
The owner of this resort hotel,
这家度假酒店的老板，
Zhao Jun, I also took photos.
赵军，我也拍过照片。
how to say?
怎么说呢？
From the data point of view
从数据来看
He gave it to me,
他给我的，
This signal tower
这座信号塔
It has been approved.
它已被批准。
I also confirmed this.
我也证实了这一点。
Telecommunications staff indeed.
确实是电信工作人员。
Install it.
安装它。
But this camera of yours,
但你的这台相机，
There's no reason why it's impossible
没有理由不可能
No reason.
没有理由。
Judging from my interactions with him,
从我和他的交往来看，
This man is very cunning.
这个人非常狡猾。
I said it on purpose
我是故意说的
thereby endangering national security.
从而危害国家安全。
He looked nervous.
他看上去很紧张。
I have no idea.
我不知道。
Feeling nervous about this,
对此感到紧张，
Or hide something?
或者隐藏什么？
I remember being near a military base
我记得在军事基地附近
around military bases.
军事基地周围。
Building height restrictions.
建筑高度限制。
From this signal tower,
从这座信号塔，
you can see
你可以看到
The entire military base.
整个军事基地。
Does this comply with the rules?
这符合规则吗？
I still need to confirm
我还需要确认
with relevant departments.
与相关部门。
Okay, I'll do it.
好吧，我会做的。
Now,
现在，
The current task is
目前的任务是
Find Han Lie's whereabouts as soon as possible.
尽快找到韩烈的下落。
I've checked.
我已经查过了。
Looks like he has a girlfriend.
看起来他有女朋友了。
But a colleague is watching him
但一位同事正在看着他
Not there either
也不在那里
Having sex with women.
与女人发生关系。
Recently he met
最近他遇到了
are business partners.
是商业伙伴。
Maybe he's hiding
也许他躲起来了
among these customers.
在这些客户之中。
OK
好的。
I'll check again.
我会再检查一下。
You are hurt.
你受伤了。
Minor injuries.
轻伤。
I originally planned to go fishing on the weekend.
原本说周末去钓鱼。
not easy
不容易
Have time alone.
有时间独处。
This cruise ship is ready for you.
这艘游轮已经为您准备好了。
Now finally...
现在终于...
like this,
就像这样，
Do you still have time for a date?
你还有时间约会吗？
before being discovered,
在被发现之前，
every day
每天
very careful.
非常小心。
Now relax.
现在放松一下。
Can you get out safely?
能安全出去，
very lucky.
非常幸运。
Why think so much?
何必想那么多呢？
I'm not here for a date.
我不是来约会的。
You are in trouble.
你有麻烦了。
Should I go?
我应该去吗？
I have to go.
我得走了。
And you?
你呢？
Usually we
通常我们
usually
通常
Quite hidden.
相当隐蔽。
And every time we meet,
而每次我们见面，
It's also because of work.
也是因为工作。
for others,
为他人，
us...
我们...
most of them are
大多数是
Supplier and customer relationships.
供应商和客户的关系。
so,
所以，
They can't doubt me.
他们不能怀疑我。
If you leave,
如果你走的话，
I will be safe.
我会安全的。
I
我
Sort it out
整理一下
Daily needs.
日常需要。
I will go abroad soon.
我很快就要出国了。
Send money to this account.
汇款至该账户。
Account name and password.
帐户名和密码。
You know everything.
你什么都知道。
At least
至少
Guaranteed
可以保证
It's been a while.
一段时间了。
Do you still want to continue?
您还想继续吗？
The company still exists
现在公司还存在
Many projects are underway.
许多项目正在进行中。
do you know,
你知道吗，
I can't leave everything behind
我不可能把一切都抛在脑后
Then walk away.
然后走开。
I know.
我知道。
everything you have now
你现在拥有的一切
Just what you want.
就是你想要的。
but...
但...
But we are different.
但我们不同。
I'm just a businessman.
我只是一个商人。
I never did anything.
我从来没有做过任何事。
They can't see my weaknesses.
他们无法发现我的弱点。
besides...
除此之外...
Someone will protect you.
有人会保护你。
Can you stop talking like that?
你能别这样说话吗？
Have you ever thought about,
你有没有想过，
one day he realized
有一天他意识到
No longer useful.
不再有用。
I gotta go
我要走了
Until that day comes.
在那一天到来之前。
This is not something you can control.
这不是你可以控制的。
Let's go together.
咱们一起去吧。
time is not up yet.
时间还没到。
I will wait for you.
我会等着你。
You have to go.
你得走了。
For me and for yourself.
为了我和你自己。
Too much?
太多了？
Two days left,
还有两天，
Our company has a cargo ship
我们公司有一艘货船
go to thailand
去泰国
You will board this ship.
你将登上这艘船。
All beach exits,
所有海滩出口，
Railway stations, bus stations, airports,
火车站、汽车站、机场、
All search warrants were issued.
所有搜查令均已发出。
The Sky Eye System is also searching.
天眼系统也在寻找。
No news yet.
目前还没有消息。
He must be hiding
他一定是躲起来了
Somewhere in Zhenhai.
镇海某处。
Account Game Hangyeol.
帐户游戏Hangyeol.
Social media accounts, phone calls.
社交媒体帐户、电话。
We monitor everything.
我们监控一切。
Nothing unusual.
没什么不寻常的。
Han Lie has been missing for three days.
韩烈已经失踪三天了。
There couldn't be any clues.
根本不可能有任何线索。
What have we overlooked?
我们忽略了什么？
What are you doing with Tuna King?
你和金枪鱼王做什么？
[Tuna King]
[金枪鱼王]
Give it to me too
也给我吧
I'll go get it now.
我现在就去拿。
This is the registration form for all customers.
这是所有客户的注册表。
Yes, no delivery is required.
是的，不需要送货。
Very good, very good, very good.
很好，很好，很好。
Until it was discovered.
直到被发现。
Thanks.
谢谢。
No need to take me there.
不用带我去。
come back next time.
下次再来。
Until it was discovered.
直到被发现。
I kept my promise.
我遵守了我的诺言。
Director Huang has left safely.
黄主任已经安全离开。
My salary has been paid.
我的工资已经付了。
Based on the highest standards,
基于最高标准，
Arrive.
到账。
from now on,
今后，
You are the real special forces.
你们是真正的特种部队。
Continue with your game.
继续你的游戏。
I won't play anymore
我不会再玩了
Don't worry.
不用担心。
next task
下一个任务
It's not a game anymore.
不再是游戏了。
all right.
全部正确。
So, you have to be more careful.
所以，你必须更加小心。
If it fails,
如果失败了，
There is no chance of repeating the mistakes of the past.
没有机会重蹈覆辙。
if you don't want
如果你不想
spend the rest of his life in jail
在监狱里度过余生
If you don't want anything to happen to your father
如果你不想让你父亲出事的话
do your work
做你的工作
Excellent.
出色地。
What about him?
那么他呢？
I once gave you a chance.
我曾经给过你一次机会。
However, since you have chosen to return,
然而，既然你选择了回归，
You guys stay
你们留下来
The closest couple.
最亲密的情侣。
Ayo.
阿哟。
I know you are sad.
我知道你很伤心。
But at least now,
但至少现在，
we already know
我们已经知道了
Is uncle okay?
叔叔平安无事了吧？
Boss Zhang is right.
张老板说得对。
I choose my own games.
我选择自己的游戏。
No one forced me.
没有人强迫我。
So, I have nothing to complain about.
所以，我没有什么可抱怨的。
And you?
你呢？
I...
我...
Isn’t this already the case?
这不已经是这样了吗？
Become a spy?
成为间谍？
regret?
后悔？
Because I chose to come back
因为我选择了回来
I won't regret it.
我不会后悔的。
Your words are very touching.
你的话很感人。
Come on, it's time for us to go home.
走吧，我们也该回家了。
Don't look.
别看。
I still have some chips.
我还有一些筹码。
I'll bet again.
我再打赌。
if i win,
如果我赢了，
I'll end it.
我会结束它。
Zhuang jam 4, Zhuang menang.
Zhuang jam 4, Zhuang menang.
win.
赢。
Thanks.
谢谢。
This scene.
这一幕。
Sangat family?
桑加特家庭？
Same wine.
同样的酒。
It turns out
事实证明
many games
许多比赛
This is doomed.
这是注定的。
as a child,
作为一个孩子，
me and my sister
我和我妹妹
Watch a show.
看剧。
He often commented on the male and female protagonists.
他经常评论男女主角。
And met by chance.
并巧合地遇见了。
and
并且
It seemed like it was meant to be.
这看起来是命中注定的。
At that time I felt
当时我就觉得
This is him
这是他
Why don't you understand romance?
你为什么不懂浪漫？
Now that I remember,
现在我想起来了，
what he said
他说的
May always be right.
可能永远是对的。
what's wrong with you?
你这人怎么回事？
I'm thinking,
我在想，
recently
最近
everything that happened
发生的一切
everything that happened.
发生的一切。
It seems to be one by one.
看起来是一一的。
There seems to be no problem.
似乎没有问题。
but you
但是你
Together
一起
Change the angle,
换个角度，
you will realize
你会意识到
obviously everything
显然一切
There are traces.
有痕迹。
Incidentally,
顺便一提，
I won the bet.
我赌赢了。
Now,
现在，
I have to settle my bet.
我必须结算我的赌注。
Let me tell you a secret.
我告诉你一个秘密。
What secret?
什么秘密？
I know your secret.
我知道你的秘密。
I met him at the Shuriken Bar.
我是在手里剑酒吧遇见他的。
Then, we went to Bangkok together.
然后，我们一起去了曼谷。
After saying that, you left without saying goodbye.
说完，你就没有告别就走了。
all of these
所有这些
Did you write the script?
剧本是你写的吧？
when i first found you
当我第一次找到你的时候
You don't look that surprised.
你看起来并不那么惊讶。
at first i thought
起初我以为
It's a pleasure.
这是一种乐趣。
But after thinking about it,
但我想了想之后，
Maybe you already know.
也许你已经知道了。
Our second task
我们的第二个任务
We will meet again.
我们会再见面的。
When I met Tony in Macau,
当我在澳门遇见Tony时，
I choose to ignore
我选择忽略
All questions.
所有的疑问。
i believe you are
我相信你是
who must
谁必须
but now,
但现在，
even me
甚至我
Myself.
我自己。
Do you know the janitor's phone number?
你知道看门人的电话号码吗？
Someone is watching.
有人在看着。
you know too.
你也知道。
All servers
所有服务器
It's their people.
是他们的人。
It looks like you are close to a spy.
看起来你离间谍很近。
What kind of spy is so trustworthy?
什么样的间谍如此信任
Someone who has to do this?
必须这样做的人？
believe
相信
You enter them.
你进入他们。
You've been a spy from the beginning, haven't you?
你从一开始就是个间谍，不是吗？
Yes, right?
是的，对吧？
listen to me.
听我说。
You just have to answer me.
你只需要回答我。
of.
的。
or not?
或不？
Always move with me.
永远和我一起行动。
Then why did you come back?
那你为什么回来？
look at me.
看着我。
I know what I said now
我现在知道我说的话了
You won't believe it.
你不会相信的。
But to come back,
但要回来，
I'm the one making the decisions.
我是做决定的人。
believe.
相信。
Why don't I believe it?
我为什么不相信呢？
Must believe.
必须相信。
Friends, do you want to write code?
朋友们，想写代码吗？
It doesn't matter, you can win again.
没关系，你还能再赢一次。
go!
去！
Harmony breeds wealth, otherwise everything goes well.
和谐孕育财富，否则万事如意。
leave.
离开。
you...
你们...
Drag people into the water.
将人们拖入水中。
Sooner or later you will get karma.
迟早你会得到业力。
go!
去！
Why are you swearing?
你为什么骂人？
Zicheng, be careful.
子成，小心点。
Let go of your hands!
放开你的手！
let go!
松手！
Yao Yao!
Yao Yao!
possible!
可能的！
Are you okay?
你没事？
Tie your hands.
绑住你的双手。
I'll take you to the hospital.
我带你去医院。
You're fine.
你没事。
No damage to nerves or muscles.
不损伤神经或肌肉。
But the blood vessels are injured
但血管受伤了
Bleeding more.
流血更多。
You have to suture the wound.
你必须缝合伤口。
this.
这。
I'll clean it up now.
我现在就清理它。
Air.
空气。
saline.
生理盐水。
I'm on the ground.
我在地上。
Get me some gauze.
给我拿点纱布来。
Come on, I'll wash it now.
来，我现在就洗。
Slow down, doctor.
慢点，医生。
It really hurts.
真的很疼。
doctor.
医生。
Will he need to be hospitalized?
他需要住院吗？
You lost a lot of blood.
你失了很多血。
It's best to stay in the hospital for observation.
最好还是留在医院观察一下。
this.
这。
I'll do it now.
我现在就做。
Wound cleaning sutures.
伤口清洁缝线。
Han Lie is already hiding
韩烈已经躲起来了
In a safe place.
在安全的地方。
After this incident has passed,
这件事情过去之后，
Just think of a way to get it out.
就想个办法把它发出去吧。
Guo An struggled to catch up.
郭安奋力追赶。
【No one can guarantee】
【没人能保证】
no one can guarantee
没有人能保证
Escort him out safely.
护送他安全出去。
There are so many things that Hangyeol takes care of.
Hangyeol 照顾的事情太多了。
Once caught,
一旦被抓到，
What is involved
涉及哪些
not only
不仅
Tsukishima.
月岛。
you...
你...
and the person behind you
和你身后的人
will be involved.
将会参与其中。
He won't tell me.
他不会告诉我。
if he doesn't say it
如果他不说的话
Is there nothing the National Security Bureau can do?
国安就不能做什么吗？
Do you think he committed a crime?
你认为他犯罪了？
Did he smuggle something?
他是不是走私了一些东西
Smuggling some goods out of the country?
走私一些货物出国？
Guoan will definitely find a way
国安一定会想办法的
Find out everything about it.
找出有关它的一切。
Contains all clues
包含所有线索
among you,
你们中间，
They won't let it go.
他们不会放过它。
you are not at all
你根本就不是
their opponents.
他们的对手。
I know.
我知道。
Han Lie is very kind to you.
韩烈对你很好。
important things in human life
人类生活中重要的事情
Not just one.
不只是一个。
You definitely know.
你肯定知道。
what is that?
那是什么？
What is most important to you.
什么对你来说最重要。
Take it.
拿去。
Some gave in.
有些人屈服了。
Buang Han Jie.
Buang Han Jie.
Your business is going well.
您的生意进展顺利。
There are people behind you protecting you.
你的背后还有人在保护你。
People who do big things don't care about small things.
做大事的人不会关心小事。
What do you want me to do?
你想要我做什么？
If I were you,
如果我是你，
Prepare a bottle of good wine
准备一瓶好酒
Say goodbye to him.
向他告别。
I'll prepare some wine for you.
我给你准备酒。
Right here, sir.
就在这里，先生。
Parker.
帕克.
help
帮助
Go to the hospital.
去医院。
OK
好的。
how? Any clues?
如何？还有线索吗？
not yet.
还没有。
Some of these hotels and restaurants
其中一些酒店和餐馆
It is a subsidiary company of Yunyi Group.
是云亿集团的下属企业。
It should be Han Jie.
应该是韩杰。
Cooperate with Yunyi Group.
与云亿集团合作。
Provide them with goods.
为他们提供货物。
Please help me arrange it
你帮我安排一下
All Yunyi Group data.
所有云亿集团数据。
OK
好的。
Chen Ting, director of Yunyi Group.
云亿集团董事陈挺。
Young businesswoman.
年轻的女商人。
It's him
是他
dengan Han Jie?
dengan Han Jie?
have photos.
有照片。
Chen Ting, Han Jie.
Chen Ting, Han Jie.
Who is that person behind?
背后那个人是谁？
Fang Lu.
Fang Lu.
Are cruise ports inspected?
游轮港口是否接受过检查？
already.
已经。
I have checked out all the cruise charter information.
我已经检查了所有游轮租赁信息。
There is no record of his registration.
没有他的注册记录。
He is very likely
他很可能
Rent someone else's yacht
租用别人的游艇
cover.
覆盖。
You check it immediately
你立即检查一下
Whether it is Chen Ting or Yunyi Group
无论是陈婷还是云亿集团
Are there any cruise ships available for long-term charter?
有没有可以长期租用的游轮？
OK
好的。
Yunyi Group
云亿集团
Long term charter of two yachts.
长期租用两艘游艇。
One of them is in the port.
其中之一在港口。
Stop at Northport Pier.
停在北港码头。
You tell the dock
你告诉码头
Get information about cruises.
获取有关游轮的信息。
OK
好的。
Pelabuhan Beigang.
Pelabuhan Beigang.
The wine was not bad.
这酒还不错。
you are visible
你是可见的
Looks very relaxed.
看起来很放松。
You sneaked out again.
你又偷偷溜出去了。
Yes, it is a red-eyed dolphin.
没错，它就是红眼海豚。
Very hard to touch.
非常难以触摸。
also,
此外，
if i don't fish
如果我不钓鱼
I can change my situation.
我可以改变我的处境。
At such a time,
在这样的时候，
Can you still fish?
你还能钓鱼吗？
I also bake cookies.
我也烤饼干。
This is for you.
这是给您的。
Can we still bake cookies here?
这里还能烤饼干吗？
Is this equipment available here?
这里有这个装备吗？
Every time you take a cruise,
每次乘坐游轮时，
Someone is serving you.
有人正在为你服务。
You don't need to worry about this.
你不需要担心这个。
Go open a bar.
去开酒吧。
I'm almost done.
我就快完成了。